<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="action_details">ic_details</string>
    <string name="specialist_altran">Specialist - Altran</string>
    <string name="fully_professional"><![CDATA[I am a fully professional creative Solution Architect in .Net/Java Solutions and Web & Analist Developer Involving with latest designing solutions and technologies is a great feel free to contact creative.]]></string>
    <string name="about_me">ABOUT ME</string>
    <string name="what_i_do">WHAT I DO ?</string>
    <string name="resume">RESUME</string>
    <string name="user_experience_design">UX/UI</string>
    <string name="product_design">Product Design</string>
    <string name="soa_design">SOA Design</string>
    <string name="mobile_solution">Mobile Solution</string>
    <string name="entrerprise_solution">Entrerprise Solution</string>
    <string name="interface_design">Interface Design</string>
    <string name="cloud_solution">Cloud Solution</string>
    <string name="net_solution">.NET Solution</string>
    <string name="java_solution">Java Solution</string>
    <string name="java">java</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="pd">pd</string>
    <string name="so">so</string>
    <string name="mo">mo</string>
    <string name="es">es</string>
    <string name="ind">ind</string>
    <string name="cs">cs</string>
    <string name="net">net</string>
    <string name="view_cv">View CV</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="what_i_do_">WHAT I DO</string>
    <string name="specialist_software_engineer">Specialist - Software Engineer</string>
    <string name="java_to_angularjs">Working on solutions to clients from Altran from Java to AngularJs</string>
    <string name="objective">OBJECTIVE</string>
    <string name="i_have_">I have been working in Portugal since 2006 to 2016, in following areas - services, billing, innovation, transports, financial markets, Marketing Digital, bank and construction. Technology used are - .Net Platform (2.0 to 4.6), Java Platform, Android Platform, programming languages C#, Javascript, Html, WCF and others. With integration to SQL Server (T-SQL) and various tools for scripting and IIS. In the last years I have explored the Cloud Computing and SOA architectures on self-studying. In the past 2 years I have the team leader of projects on agile methodologies and scrum methods. Simultaneously, I have been developing my skills in the Cloud Computing with the self-learning of the Azure Platform and Courses online of the Microsoft Academy. In the past 2 years, I have worked as a former, project and team manager, and have been responsible for the course of Asp.Net and Azure Integration. I can work on different projects in parallel always focusing on the quality of my work. I\'m keen on everything I do and always expect the best from myself. I also try to keep up to date as much as possible through constant trainings. I am a communicative person and try to deal as better as possible with any person.</string>
</resources>